{
    "subject": "resource/Acharya_Ramlochan_Saran",
    "predicate": "property/deathDate",
    "object": "1971-05-14",
    "human_readable": "Acharya Ramlochan Saran died on 1971-05-14.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8973966240882874,
            "question": "When did Acharya Ramlochan Saran die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8524988889694214,
            "question": "What year was Acharya Ramlochan Saran's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7938562035560608,
            "question": "In what month did Acharya Ramlochan Saran die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7613738179206848,
            "question": "Were there any notable events that occurred around the time of Acharya Ramlochan Saran's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.697779655456543,
            "question": "Was Acharya Ramlochan Saran alive in the 20th century?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6908265948295593,
            "question": "How old was Acharya Ramlochan Saran at the time of his death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6718025207519531,
            "question": "What day of the week was Acharya Ramlochan Saran's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6404102444648743,
            "question": "What was Acharya Ramlochan Saran known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4477878212928772,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Acharya Ramlochan Saran's life and work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41683080792427063,
            "question": "Who were some influential people in Acharya Ramlochan Saran's life and work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Acharya Ramlochan Saran died on 1971-05-14.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1940_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Acharya Ramlochan Saran's life and work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1940_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was Acharya Ramlochan Saran known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1940_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What day of the week was Acharya Ramlochan Saran's death?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1940_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1940_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1940_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1940_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1940_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1940_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1940_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1940_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1940_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1940_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1940_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports that Acharya Ramlochan Saran died on May 14, 1971. This is mentioned multiple times across different files."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents supports the statement that Acharya Ramlochan Saran died on May 14, 1971. This is explicitly mentioned in multiple files, confirming the date of his death."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}